(Zack:)I was wondering about that.
(Howard:)You could put it in a
satellite or a rocket,
(Howard:)and it'll run forever.
(Howard:)Cool.
(Zack:)Could it be used for
missiles and war stuff?
(Howard:)Yeah, but we didn't
create it for weapons.
(Leonard:)And I doubt the military
would be interested
(Leonard:)in our little
guidance system.
(Zack:)Is it better than
the one they use now?
A lot!
Way better.
(Zack:)Huh.
(Zack:)You sure you guys are smart?
“H-O” gauge trains
are 1/87 scale.
“N” gauge are
1/160 scale.
(Sheldon:)And that brings us
to “Z” gauge, at a
“you could easily swallow it,
don't ask how I know,” 1/220.
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry, I have to ask.
(Sheldon:)When I was five, I ingested
a “Z” gauge locomotive.
(Sheldon:)I spent the next three days
saying, “I think I can pass it,
(Sheldon:)I think I can pass it,
I think I can pass it.”